<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sessions on Beam Summit 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sessions on Beam Summit 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 07:51:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The nitty-gritty of moving data with Beam</title>
      <link>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/nitty-gritty-moving-data-with-beam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/nitty-gritty-moving-data-with-beam/</guid>
      <description>In this session, you won&amp;rsquo;t learn about joins or windows or timers or any other advanced features of Beam. Instead, we will focus on the real-world complexity that comes from simply moving data from one system to another safely. How do we model data as it passes from one transform to another? How do we handle errors? How do we test the system? How do we organize the code to make the pipeline configurable for different source and destination systems?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: Building big data pipelines for deep learning</title>
      <link>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/workshop-building-big-data-pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/workshop-building-big-data-pipelines/</guid>
      <description>We will work through an end-to-end example of using the Python Beam SDK to build maintainable, reliable, and scalable production pipelines for deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: First steps with Apache Beam - Writing portable pipelines using Java, Python, Go, Kotlin</title>
      <link>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/first-steps-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.beamsummit.org/sessions/first-steps-workshop/</guid>
      <description>This workshop is for participants who are getting started with Apache Beam. We will get hands-on writing Beam pipelines, as well as discuss the fundamentals of Beam programming model and SDKs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>